{
    "subject": "resource/Cycling_at_the_1992_Summer_Olympics_\u2013_Men's_team_time_trial",
    "predicate": "ontology/goldMedalist",
    "object": "resource/Uwe_Peschel",
    "human_readable": "Uwe Peschel won a gold medal in Cycling at the 1992 Summer Olympics \u2013 Men's team time trial.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9708303213119507,
            "question": "Did Uwe Peschel win a gold medal in cycling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9587866067886353,
            "question": "Name the event where Uwe Peschel won a gold medal."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9376726746559143,
            "question": "In what year did Uwe Peschel win a gold medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.920215904712677,
            "question": "What event did Uwe Peschel win a gold medal in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9082533717155457,
            "question": "At which Olympic Games did Uwe Peschel win gold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9039783477783203,
            "question": "What is the name of the cyclist who won a gold medal at the 1992 Summer Olympics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7210893034934998,
            "question": "What kind of Olympics did Uwe Peschel compete in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6781008243560791,
            "question": "What color medal did Uwe Peschel win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6699919104576111,
            "question": "What sport was Uwe Peschel competing in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5596204996109009,
            "question": "Was Uwe Peschel competing individually or as part of a team?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Uwe Peschel won a gold medal in Cycling at the 1992 Summer Olympics \u2013 Men's team time trial.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7363_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport was Uwe Peschel competing in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7363_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What color medal did Uwe Peschel win?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7363_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of Olympics did Uwe Peschel compete in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7363_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7363_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information that supports the statement \"Uwe Peschel won a gold medal in Cycling at the 1992 Summer Olympics \u2013 Men's team time trial.\" Specifically, the document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7363/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt` states that \"Uwe Peschel, son of Axel Peschel, was a road cyclist who was on the gold medal-winning German 100 km team time trial at the 1992 Barcelona Olympics.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}